<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="factstrings">
		<item>For every human being on earth, there are about 200 million
			insects. This is not including Driders.</item>
		<item>The harmonica is the world\'s most second most popular
			instrument, right behind hitting something with a stick.</item>
		<item>By the time they are 65 years old, most Americans have watched
			more than nine years worth of stupid pet tricks.</item>
		<item>A punch to the face can cause a tooth to fall out.</item>
		<item>If you stretched all the nerves in the body from end to end,
			they would be about 47 miles long. I\'ve only managed to stretch mine
			32 so far, but hope to eventually hit 45.</item>
		<item>Humans have more than 600 muscles in their bodies, not
			including "the wang".</item>
		<item>Rubber bands last longer when refrigerated.</item>
		<item>Peanuts are one of the ingredients of dynamite. That\'s why
			they explode when you throw them.</item>
		<item>There are 1293 ways to make change for a platinum piece.
		</item>
		<item>The average person\'s left hand does 56% of the typing. Lefties are 
			up to something.</item>
		<item>A shark is the only fish that can blink with both eyes.
		</item>
		<item>There are more chickens than people in the world, but that\'s
			because a lot of people *are* chicken.</item>
		<item>Two-thirds of the world\'s eggplant is grown in New Jersey.
		</item>
		<item>The longest one-syllable word in the English language is
			"schlong."</item>
		<item>All of my clocks are stuck at 4:28.</item>
		<item>No word in the English language rhymes with month, orange,
			silver or purple. but you can still rhyme them, like purple with
			"girl pull"</item>
		<item>"Dreamt" is the only English word that ends in the letters
			"mt."</item>
		<item>All 50 states are listed across the top of the Lincoln
			Memorial on the back of the $5 bill.</item>
		<item>Almonds are a member of the peach family. That\'s why they\'re
			fuzzy.</item>
		<item>ur mom was born in a ladies\' room during a dance.</item>
		<item>Maine is the only state whose name is just one syllable.
		</item>
		<item>The largest cabbage weighed 144 lbs. His name was Steve.
		</item>
		<item>There are only four words in the English language which end in
			"-dous": tremendous, horrendous, stupendous, and hazardous. </item>
		<item>A cat has 32 muscles in each ear. I counted last time I took
			one apart.</item>
		<item>An ostrich\'s eye is bigger than its brain. That\'s why they
			were goggles when hiding in the sand.</item>
		<item>Tigers have striped skin, not just stripped fur- it\'s true! I 
			shaved one to make sure.</item>

		<item>Al Capone\'s business card said he was a used furniture dealer.
		</item>
		<item>The characters Bert and Ernie on Sesame Street were named
			after Bert the cop and Ernie the taxi driver in Frank Capra\'s "Its A
			Wonderful Life."</item>
		<item>A dragonfly has a life span of 24 seconds.</item>
		<item>A goldfish has a memory span of three seconds.</item>
		<item>It\'s impossible to sneeze with your eyes open. If you manage
			to do it, you eye will pop out of socket.</item>
		<item>The giant squid has the largest eyes in the world. "The better
			to see you with," it claims.</item>
		<item>In England, the Speaker of the House is not allowed to speak,
			however he\'s also the only one allowed to breakdance.</item>
		<item>The microwave was invented after a researcher walked by a
			radar tube and a chocolate bar melted in his pocket.</item>
		<item>Mr. Rogers was an ordained minister. That explains his love of
			children.</item>
		<item>There are 336 dimples on a regulation golf ball.</item>
		<item>"Stewardesses" is the longest word that is typed with only the
			left hand. I know you like to type with only the left hand quite often
			...</item>
		<item>Many hamsters blink one eye at a time, but they will get
			pissed if you call them blinky.</item>
		<item>The inventor of the flushing toilet was Earl Shitter.</item>
		<item>Your bed is home to over 6 billion dust mites. Mine just has
			fleas.</item>
		<item>Plastic lawn flamingos outnumber real flamingos in the U.S.A.
			They often are better with drunken conversations.</item>
		<item>Whitby, Ontario has more donut stores per capita than any
			other place in the world. EXCEPT MY PANTS!</item>
		<item>Starfish have no brain. That\'s why most run for office by the
			time they\'re 25.</item>
		<item>Dolphins sleep with one eye open. They don\'t trust the
			lobsters.</item>
		<item>Ernest Vincent Wright wrote a novel with over 50,000 words,
			none of which contained the letter "E".</item>
		<item>Bulls are color blind. Tell that to the guy in the superman
			cape who got gored.</item>
		<item>A can of SPAM is opened every 4 seconds. a can of whoopass is
			opened on a spammer only once a year.  </item>
		<item>"Babe" was played by over 48 pigs. They were all delicious
			after filming.</item>
		<item>Mosquitoes have 47 teeth- the better to bite you with. AAAH,
			SHARP TEETH RUN NO BITE NO BAD MOSQUITO</item>
		<item>Lip stick contains fish scales and bull semen.</item>
		<item>The Poison Arrow frog has enough poison to kill 2200 people
			and a goat.</item>
		<item>The largest known kidney stone weighed 1.36 kilograms. It was
			later used in his fireplace.</item>
		<item>Kidney stones come in any shade from yellow to brown.</item>
		<item>Women blink twice as many times as men do. Mascara weighs down 
		eyelashes, which causes excess blinking, which causes crows feet.</item>
		<item>A bowling pin only has to tilt 7.5 degrees in order to fall
			down, much like a drunk halfling.</item>
		<item>The first episode of Leave It To Beaver aired on October 4,
			1957. Heh, I said beaver.</item>
		<item>Beaver Cleaver\'s locker number is 9. I wrote a song about it-
			it goes like this "LOCKER NUMBER 9 OOOH LOCKER NUMBER NINE AAAH
			BEAVERS LOCKER YEAH!"</item>
		<item>The life span of a taste bud is ten days, unless you make it a
			habit to eat things that are on fire.</item>
		<item>Pi has been calculated to 2,260,321,363 digits. I can count to
			potato.</item>
		<item>The billionth digit in Pi is 9. or maybe 7. Shit, let me start
			over...</item>
		<item>The first 100 numbers of Pi are:
			3.14159265358979323846264338327950288419716939937510S8209749445923078l64062862O8998628034B253421170679 haha I snuck letters in.
		</item>
		<item>A stretched out Slinky is 87 feet long. So if you\'re looking
			for your slinky, don\'t ask me where it is cause I haven\'t seen it.
		</item>
		<item>An iguana can stay under water for 28 minutes, unless he was
			carrying a straw.</item>
		<item>Emus can\'t walk backwards, but they can projectile poo.
		</item>
		<item>A group of unicorns is called a blessing. Tastes great with
			pepper.</item>
		<item>A group of kangaroos is called a mob. Tastes great with salt.
		</item>
		<item>A group of whales is called a pod. Tastes great with lemon.
		</item>
		<item>A group of geese is called a gaggle. Tastes great with curry.
		</item>
		<item>A group of owls is called a parliament. Tastes funkadalic with
			oregano.</item>
		<item>A group of ravens is called a murder. Tastes great cold and with basil.
		</item>
		<item>A group of bears is called a sleuth. Tastes great with
			paprika.</item>
		<item>12 or more cows is called a flink. Tastes great with steak
			seasoning....mmm steak.</item>
		<item>A baby oyster is called a spat. Sorry I don\'t eat spat.
		</item>
		<item>Chickens can\'t swallow while they are upside down. The don\'t
			drink well upside-down either.</item>
		<item>In the October 22, 1945 edition of Life magazine there was a
			picture of a chicken with its head cut off. His name was Mike. No
			really, look it up. Go now. Seriously. ALL MY FACTS ARE TRUE.</item>
		<item>The average garden variety caterpillar has 248 muscles in its
			head.</item>
		<item>Pinocchio was made of pine.</item>
		<item>The largest pumpkin weighed 1262 lbs, 1101 lbs after they 
		removed Peter\'s wife. It was delicious.</item>
		<item>A mule won\'t sink in quicksand but a donkey will.</item>
		<item>More people are killed annually by donkeys than in airplane
			crashes.</item>
		<item>Alfred Hitchcock had no belly button- it was removed
			during surgery.</item>
		<item>The average human produces 10,000 gallons of saliva in a
			lifetime. I keep mine in a jar.</item>
		<item>A silver piece has 119 grooves around the edge.</item>
		<item>A copper piece has 118 ridges around the edge.</item>
		<item>Cranberry Jello is the only kind that contains real fruit.
		</item>
		<item>The plastic things on the end of shoelaces are called aglets.
		</item>
		<item>Every time you lick a stamp you consume 1/10 of a calorie. Every time 
		you stick a tramp you gain an STD.
		</item>
		<item>The pound sign # is called an octothorpe.</item>
		<item>Maine is the toothpick capital of the world. They\'re all way
			too picky.</item>
		<item>New Jersey has a spoon museum with over 5,400 spoons from
			almost all the states.</item>
		<item>There was once a town in West Virginia called "6". I took a
			number "2" there.</item>
		<item>Singapore only has one train station, but that\'s because they
			have 425 metro stations.</item>
		<item>The parking meter was invented in North Dakota.</item>
		<item>Napolean made his battle plans in a sandbox. The neighbors
			cats supplied the German pieces.</item>
		<item>Roman Emperor Caligula made his horse a senator- and no, it
			wasn\'t Ed. Common mistake.</item>
		<item>The green stuff on the occasional freak potato chip is
			chlorophyll.</item>
		<item>If you ate too many carrots you would turn orange, even your
			nails!</item>
		<item>Pluto\'s orbit crosses Neptune\'s making Pluto the eighth planet
			from the sun. It has been that way since 1979 and was until I told it
			"STFU you\'re not a planet" and it got back in it\'s place.</item>
		<item>The earth is approx. 6,588,000,000,000,000,000 tons, or
			approximately half the weight of ur mom.</item>
		<item>The force of 1 billion people jumping at the same time is
			equal to 500 tons of TNT- don\'t tell china tho.</item>
		<item>Popeye was 5\'6".</item>
		<item>Howdy Doody had 48 freckles. Heh, I said doody.</item>
		<item>The first word spoken on the moon was "uh".</item>
		<item>Neil Armstrong stepped on the moon with his left foot first.
			This is because he had two of them, according to his dance
			instructor.</item>
		<item>The average speed of Heinz ketchup leaving the bottle is 25
			miles per year.</item>
		<item>The percent of women who wash their hands after leaving a
			restroom is 80 percent. The percent of men who wash their hands after using
			a restroom is 55 percent. the percent who lie about this is potato.
		</item>
		<item>There are 333 toilet paper squares on a toilet paper roll. I
			counted 1628 rolls and figured out the average.</item>
		<item>The Eifel Tower has 2,503,401 rivets in it.</item>
		<item>"Jaws" is the most common name for a goldfish.
			"psycho-grinning snackiefood" is a close second.</item>
		<item>The average American eats 2 donuts a day. mmmm donuts. I may have shifted the
			the median.
		</item>
		<item>The longest word in the Old Testament is
			Malhershalahashbazoids.</item>
		<item>The longest time a person has been in a coma is 37 years.
		</item>
		<item>Every minute in the U.S 6 people turn 17.</item>
		<item>It takes the Where\'s Waldo artist one month to complete a
			drawing, but no one has seen him in decades.</item>
		<item>2500 lefties die each year using products designed for
			righties.</item>
		<item>A baby is born every 7 seconds. How many are yours?</item>
		<item>10 tons of space dust fall on the Earth everyday. Most of it
			is snorted up by David Bowie who named a record after me.</item>
		<item>On average, a 4 year old child asks 437 questions a day. Over
			80% are "why?"</item>
		<item>Blue and white are the most common school colors.</item>
		<item>Swimming pools in Phoenix, Arizona, pick up 20 pounds of dust
			a year. Unfortunately it is immune to brooms.</item>
		<item>The first message tapped by Samuel Morse over his invention
			the telegraph was: "What hath God wrought? Can I get a cheeseburger?"
		</item>
		<item>The first words spoken by over Alexander Bell over the
			telephone were: Watson, "please come here, my head is stuck."
		</item>
		<item>The first words spoken by Thomas Edison over the phonograph
			were: "Mary had an obese lamb"</item>
		<item>The three words in the English language with the letters uu
			are: vacuum, residuum and continuum.</item>
		<item>A baby in Florida was named:
			Truewilllaughinglifebuckyboomermanifestdestiny. His middle name is
			George James.</item>
		<item>It is illegal to ride a street car on Sunday if you have been
			eating garlic in Toronto, Ontario, Canada. That is a good law cause I
			don\'t like stinky people.</item>
		<item>In a normal life time an American will eat 200 pounds of
			peanuts and 10,000 pounds of meat. Women will eat slightly more meat
			*wink*</item>
		<item>A new book is published every 13 minutes in America. Most are
			utter crap, like mine</item>
		<item>America\'s best selling ice-cream flavour is vanilla. It goes
			with everything; like shoes.</item>
		<item>Americans eat 18 billion hot dogs a year, but buy 24 billion
			buns.</item>
		<item>Americans eat 134 pounds of sugar a year. They then wonder why
			they\'re fat.</item>
		<item>Every year the sun loses 360 million tons of gas... and never
			excuses itself.</item>
		<item>Because of Animal Crackers, many kids until they reach the age
			of ten, believe a bear is as tall as a giraffe.</item>
		<item>You can tell if a skunk is around if you smell only .000 000
			000 000 071 ounce of its spray. I drank a teaspoon of it once on 
			a dare when I worked at the zoo. I both won and lost that dare.</item>
		<item>Animal breeders in Russia once claimed to have bred sheep with
			blue wool. They called him Steely Blue Bah.</item>
		<item>Penguins are the only bird that can leap into the air like
			porpoises. They also smell fishy.</item>
		<item>India has 50 million monkeys. Most have promising careers in
			the IT industry answering phones.</item>
		<item>By some unknown means, an iguana can end its own life. I think
			it involves a stapler.</item>
		<item>Americans spend around $3 billion for cat and dog food a year.
		</item>
		<item>Pigs can cover a mile in 7.5 minutes when running at top
			speed, but only if greased.</item>
		<item>You breathe about 10 million times a year.</item>
		<item>The colder the room you sleep in, the better the chances are
			that you\'ll have a bad dream.</item>
		<item>The first non-human to win an Oscar was Mickey Mouse.</item>
		<item>The Gulf Stream could carry a message in a bottle at an
			average of 4 miles per hour.</item>
		<item>The bullseye on a dartboard must be 5 feet 8 inches off the
			ground or resting atop a dwarf\'s head.</item>
		<item>The foot is the most common body part bitten by insects,
			unless you count crabs.</item>
		<item>The most common time for a wake up call is 7am.</item>
		<item>The doorbell was invented in 1831 by Robert Dorbel</item>
		<item>The are 255 squares on a Scrabble board- six more than a chess
			board.</item>
		<item>The electric shaver was patented on November 6, 1928.</item>
		<item>There are 500 sheets of paper in a ream.</item>
		<item>The monkey wrench was invented by Charles Moncke.</item>
		<item>Japan is the largest exporter of frog\'s legs. Guess who they
			sell them to?</item>
		<item>There are seven points on the Statue of Liberty\'s crown. Plus
			she isn\'t wearing panties.</item>
		<item>There are approx. 550 hairs in the eyebrow... I wish I had
			eyebrows:\(</item>
		<item>The most common non-contagious disease in the world is tooth
			decay.</item>
		<item>The shell constitutes 12 percent of an egg\'s weight.</item>
		<item>A squid has 10 tentacles. That\'s a lot of nads.</item>
		<item>A snail\'s reproductive organs are in its head. That\'s why I
			call them dobule-dong-heads.</item>
		<item>A cow\'s only sweat glands are in its nose.</item>
		<item>The word "AND" appears 46,277 times in the Bible, except in
			the original aramaic where it is not seen.</item>
		<item>The first word played in the Scrabble rules demonstration game
			is "horny".</item>
		<item>The telephone\'s U.S. patent number is 174,465.</item>
		<item>The typical person goes to the bathroom 6 times a day. I only
			go once tho since I\'m only allowed one break a day. That\'s why I keep
			all those mountain dew bottles around.</item>
		<item>There are 17 steps leading up to Sherlock Holme\'s apartment.
		</item>
		<item>When a horned toad is angry, it squirts blood from it\'s eyes.
			You should see what an Angry toad does when it\'s horny 0~0</item>
		<item>Napoleon was terrified of cats. What a pussy.</item>
		<item>The first Lifesaver flavor was ginger.</item>
		<item>The typical American eats 263 eggs a year, unless you count
			spider eggs.</item>
		<item>The ballpoint pen was invented in 1938 by Laszlo and George
			Biro.</item>
		<item>The fastest growing nail is on the middle finger- want to see
			mine grow?</item>
		<item>The parking meter was invented by C.C. Magee in 1935.</item>
		<item>In 1961, an IBM 7090 computer calculated Pi to 100 265 digits.
		</item>
		<item>The human body weighs forty times more than the brain, except
			americans where it\'s 80 times more on account of the small brain and
			large ass.</item>
		<item>After eating too much, your hearing is less sharp.</item>
		<item>A person swallows approximately 295 times while eating dinner,
			unless they\'re half snake, in which case it\'s only once.</item>
		<item>The oldest known vegetable is the pea. hehe... "pee".</item>
		<item>Jack is the most common name in nursery rhymes. Second is
			Eduardo.</item>
		<item>The avocado has the most calories of any fruit. That\'s why
			they\'re so tasty and smooth.</item>
		<item>The first zoo in the USA was in Philadelphia.</item>
		<item>The letter N ends all Japanese words not ending in a vowel.
		</item>
		<item>France has the highest per capita consumption of cheese. I
			think it\'s because they wine so much.</item>
		<item>The hardest bone in the human body is the jawbone. That\'s why
			you gotta hit it extra hard.</item>
		<item>4000 people are injured by teapots each year.</item>
		<item>The typical American consumes 87 pounds of cheese each year.
		</item>
		<item>The shortest English word that contains the letters A, B, C,
			D, E, and F is feedback.</item>
		<item>The ostrich has a 46 foot long small intestine.</item>
		<item>The state of California raises the most turkeys out of all of
			the states. Example: Scientology.</item>
		<item>The most sensitive finger on the human hand is the index
			finger.</item>
		<item>George Washington Carver invented peanut coffee, which wasn\'t
			as big a hit as carabou milk..</item>
		<item>The typical hen lays 19 dozen eggs a year. I usually manage
			one or two a day.</item>
		<item>Stainless steel was invented by Harry Brearley in 1913.
		</item>
		<item>A scallop has 35 blue eyes. That\'s really creepy.</item>
		<item>The left leg of a chicken is more tender than the right one.
		</item>
		<item>The only dog that doesn\'t have a pink tongue is the chow. It\'s
			from being bred to eat their own poop.</item>
		<item>Iceland was the first country to legalize abortion in 1935.
		</item>
		<item>The giraffe has the highest blood pressure of any animal. It\'s
			REALLY cool when you chase them between two telephone poles and it
			decapitates them. it rains blood for like 30 minutes!</item>
		<item>The dumbest domesticated animal is the beagle.</item>
		<item>Russia has the most movie theaters in the world.</item>
		<item>Albert Blake Dick invented the mimeograph machine.</item>
		<item>The strongest muscle in the human body is the tongue. I do
			pushups with mine.</item>
		<item>The most fatal car accidents occur on Saturday, usually 2-3am
		</item>
		<item>An Oscar weighs seven pounds.</item>
		<item>It takes the typical person seven minutes to fall asleep.
			Lucky bastards.</item>
		<item>Gabriel Guenter Fahrenheit invented the mercury thermometer.
		</item>
		<item>The Eiffel Tower has 1792 steps- that is in memory of the year
			it was built.</item>
		<item>The mongoose was barred live entry into the U.S. in 1902. They
			didn\'t want them getting loose and killing the native cobra
			population.</item>
		<item>Ants stretch when they wake up in the morning.</item>
		<item>Thomas Edison, lightbulb inventor, was afraid of the dark.
		</item>
		<item>About 3000 years ago, most Egyptians died by the time they
			were 30.</item>
		<item>A sneeze travels out your mouth at over 6000 m.p.h.</item>
		<item>The average person has over 1,460 dreams a year.</item>
		<item>Lightning strikes about 6,000 times per minute on this planet.
		</item>
		<item>Owls are the only birds who can see the color blue. They\'s why
			they often fly into lakes.</item>
		<item>A jellyfish is 95 percent water, just like humans.</item>
		<item>The elephant is the only mammal that can\'t jump- it can dance
			tho like in the toilet paper commercials.</item>
		<item>The penguin is the only bird who can swim, but not fly.
		</item>
		<item>America once issued a 5-cent bill. morgajel pays me in those.
		</item>
		<item>Like fingerprints, everyone\'s tongue print is different.
		</item>
		<item>Fortune cookies were actually invented in America, in 1918, by
			Charles Jung Wang.</item>
		<item>You know what I have in common with a giraffe? we both can
			clean our ears with our 21-inch tongues.</item>
		<item>Chewing gum while peeling onions will keep you from crying.
		</item>
		<item>Bats always turn left when exiting a cave.</item>
		<item>Fingernails grow nearly 4 times faster than toenails.</item>
		<item>You blink about 84,000,000 times a year.</item>
		<item>In England, in the 1880\'s, "Pants" was considered a dirty
			word.</item>
		<item>A toothpick is the object most often choked on by Americans.
		</item>
		<item>Every 45 seconds, a house catches on fire in the United
			States. And if the police ask, I was here all day.</item>
		<item>The sun is 330,330 times larger than the earth and only 157 times larger than ur mom.</item>
		<item>A hummingbird weighs less than a penny.</item>
		<item>A cockroach will live nine days without it\'s head, before it
			starves to death.</item>
		<item>The most used letter in the English alphabet is \'E\', and \'Q\'
			is the least used.</item>
		<item>Dogs and cats, like humans, are either right or left handed...
			you can tell by what paw they use to write.</item>
		<item>The opposite sides of a d6 always add up to seven.</item>
		<item>Men are 6 times more likely to be struck by lighting than
			women- usually because they\'re pitching a tent.</item>
		<item>Of all the words in the English language, the word "set" has
			the most definitions.</item>
		<item>Apples are more efficient than caffeine in keeping people
			awake in the mornings.</item>
		<item>Smelling bananas and/or green apples (smelling, not eating)
			can help you lose weight.</item>
		<item>After eating, a housefly regurgitates its food and then eats
			it again! I tried it, but didn\'t see the appeal.</item>
		<item>When someone annoys you, it takes 42 muscles to frown, but it
			only takes 4 muscles to extend your leg to kick them in the groin.
		</item>
		<item>Coca-Cola was originally green.</item>
		<item>Hong Kong has the most Rolls Royce\'s per capita.</item>
		<item>Alaska is the state with highest percent of people who walk to
			work.</item>
		<item>28 percent of Africa is wilderness.</item>
		<item>38 percent of America is wilderness.</item>
		<item>It costs $6400 to raise a medium size dog to age of 11.
		</item>
		<item>Average number of people airborne over the U.S. during any
			given hour: 61,000.</item>
		<item>70 percent of Americans have visited Disneyland/World. Most of
			them think Mickey is real.</item>
		<item>Intelligent people have more copper and zinc in their hair.
			The smartest ones don\'t even bother growing hair.</item>
		<item>The youngest pope was 11 years old. All the older cardinals
			invited him to the sleepovers.... that\'s creepy.</item>
		<item>Iceland consumes more Coca-Cola per capita than any other
			country.</item>
		<item>The sentence "The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog."
			uses every letter in the alphabet and was developed by Western Union
			to test telex/twx communications.</item>
		<item>Average life span of a major league baseball: 7 pitches.
		</item>
		<item>The San Francisco Cable cars are the only "mobile" National
			Monuments.</item>
		<item>The only 15-letter word that can be spelled without repeating
			a letter "uncopyrightable," which is copyrighted.</item>
		<item>Did you know that there are dirt flavored PEZ?</item>
		<item>The reason firehouses have circular stairways is from the days
			of yore when the engines were pulled by horses. The horses were
			stabled on the ground floor and learned how to walk up regular
			staircases.</item>
		<item>When opossums are playing \'possum, they are not "playing."
			They actually pass out from being cowards.</item>
		<item>The Main Library at Indiana University sinks over an inch
			every year because, when it was built, engineers failed to take into
			account the weight of all the books that would occupy the building.
		</item>
		<item>111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321</item>
		<item>Clans of long ago that wanted to get rid of unwanted people
			(without killing them) used to burn their houses down - hence the
			expression "to get fired." I\'ve fired at least 270 people.</item>
		<item>Only two people signed the Declaration of Independence on July
			4th, John Hancock and Charles Thomson. Most of the rest signed on
			August 2, but the last signature wasn\'t added until 5 years later.
		</item>
		<item>The longest recorded flight of a chicken is thirteen seconds.I
			threw him really hard, too.</item>
		<item>David Prowse was the guy in the Darth Vader suit in Star Wars.
			He spoke all of Vader\'s lines, and didn\'t know his voice was going to
			be dubbed over by James Earl Jones until he saw the screening of the
			movie.</item>
		<item>The Pentagon, in Arlington, Virginia, has twice as many
			bathrooms as is necessary. When it was built in the 1940s, the state
			of Virginia still had segregation laws requiring separate toilet
			facilities for blacks and whites.</item>
		<item>The cruise liner, Queen Elizabeth II, moves only six inches
			for each gallon of diesel fuel that it burns.</item>
		<item>The highest point in Pennsylvania is lower than the lowest
			point in Colorado.</item>
		<item>Nutmeg is extremely poisonous if injected intravenously. So is
			air, soap, and coagulant.</item>
		<item>If you have three quarters, four dimes, and four pennies, you
			have $1.19. You also have the largest amount of money in coins
			without being able to make change for a dollar- \'bout tree fiddy.
		</item>
		<item>The only two days of the year in which there are no
			professional sports games (MLB, NBA, NHL, or NFL) are the day before
			and the day after the Major League All-star Game.</item>
		<item>Only one person in two billion will live to be 116 or older.
		</item>
		<item>Pound for pound, hamburgers cost more than new cars, but I
			usually only by my hamburger by the quarter pound.</item>
		<item>The 3 most valuable brand names on earth: Marlboro, Coca-Cola,
			and Budweiser, in that order... I think that may be out of date.</item>
		<item>It\'s possible to lead a cow upstairs...but not downstairs.
			Just remember to push real hard and watch where you put your hand :/.
		</item>
		<item>Ninety percent of New York City cabbies are recently arrived
			immigrants.</item>
		<item>In 10 minutes, a hurricane releases more energy than all the
			world\'s nuclear weapons combined.</item>
		<item>Reno, Nevada is west of Los Angeles, California.</item>
		<item>The cigarette lighter was invented before the match. Both are
			acceptable tools for arsonists.</item>
		<item>If you yelled for 8 years, 7 months and 6 days, you would have
			produced enough sound energy to heat one cup of coffee.</item>
		<item>The human heart creates enough pressure when it pumps out to
			the body to squirt blood 30 feet.</item>
		<item>Banging your head against a wall uses 150 calories an hour. I
			figure I have lost a few pounds today.</item>
		<item>On average people fear spiders more than they do death. Why?
			cause death doesn\'t give you the jibblies as easily.</item>
		<item>You can\'t kill yourself by holding your breath. Unless you do
			it while swimming, in which case you\'re dumb.</item>
		<item>You are more likely to be killed by a champagne cork than by a
			poisonous spider.</item>
		<item>Right-handed people live, on average, nine years longer than
			left-handed people do.</item>
		<item>In ancient Egypt, Priests plucked every hair from their
			bodies, including their eyebrows and nutsatchels..</item>
		<item>A crocodile cannot stick its tongue out. Taunt them about it.
		</item>
		<item>Butterflies taste with their feet. Coincidentally, they taste
			like feet after stepping on a butterfly.</item>
		<item>A cat\'s urine glows under a blacklight.</item>
		<item>The first couple to be shown in bed together on prime time
			television were Fred and Wilma Flintstone.</item>
		<item>The Ten Commandments contain 297 words.</item>
		<item>The Bill of Rights is stated in 463 words.</item>
		<item>Lincoln\'s Gettysburg Address contains 266 words.</item>
		<item>A recent federal directive to regulate the price of cabbage
			contains 26,911 words.</item>
		<item>There are more collect calls made on Father\'s Day than on any
			other day. Most are made from prison.</item>
		<item>Every day more money is printed for monopoly than the US
			Treasury.</item>
		<item>Men can read smaller print than women, women can hear better
			than men.</item>
		<item>The world\'s youngest parents were 8 and 9 and lived in China
			in 1910.</item>
		<item>Honey is the only food that doesn\'t spoil. It\'s delicious,
			too. I like to stick my head in a bees nest and drink it.</item>
		<item>Half of all Americans live within 50 miles of their
			birthplace.</item>
		<item>The nursery rhyme Ring Around the Rosey is a rhyme about the
			bubonic plague. Infected people with the plague would get red
			circular sores (Ring around the Rosey...). These sores would smell
			very bad so people would hide flowers on their bodies in an attempt
			to mask the smell ("pocket full of posies..."). People who died from
			the plague would be burned to reduce the spread of the disease
			("ashes, ashes, we all fall down").</item>
		<item>The citrus soda 7-UP was created in 1929; "7" was selected
			because the original containers were 7 ounces. "UP" indicated that it
			gave you an erection..</item>
		<item>Mosquito repellents don\'t repel. They hide you. The spray
			blocks the mosquito\'s sensors so they don\'t know you\'re there. I oten
			spray myself with pig feces which makes me invisible to uppity-ups.
		</item>
		<item>Dentists have recommended that a toothbrush be kept at least 6
			feet away from a toilet to avoid airborne particles resulting from
			the flush. Thinks about that next time you brush, poomouth.</item>
		<item>The liquid inside young coconuts can be used as substitute for
			blood plasma, unless you\'re a vampire.</item>
		<item>American car horns beep in the tone of F.</item>
		<item>No piece of paper can be folded more than 7 times. I\'ve tried.
		</item>
		<item>1 in every 4 Americans has appeared on television. I know I
			have.</item>
		<item>You burn more calories sleeping than you do watching
			television. arguing on the internet burns more than both.</item>
		<item>Oak trees do not produce acorns until they are fifty years of
			age or older. Think about it- how many times have you seen a
			50-year-old\'s nuts?</item>
		<item>The first product to have a bar code was Wrigley\'s gum. it\'s
			Wriggley.</item>
		<item>The king of hearts is the only king without a mustache. That\'s
			because he was only 11.</item>
		<item>A Boeing 747s wingspan is longer than the Wright brother\'s
			first flight.</item>
		<item>American Airlines saved $40,000 in 1987 by eliminating 1 olive
			from each salad served in first-class.</item>
		<item>Venus is the only planet that rotates clockwise. They must
			keep it in australia, cause their toilets flush that way too.
		</item>
		<item>The first CD pressed in the US was Bruce Springsteen\'s "Born
			in the USA."</item>
		<item>The 57 on the Heinz ketchup bottle represents the number of
			varieties of pickles the company once had. I haven\'t liked pickles
			since the pickle thread on fark. If you don\'t know what that is, don\'t a
			google image search for Fark Pickle Thread.</item>
		<item>Most dust particles in your house are made from dead skin.
			mmmm, tasty.</item>
		<item>Timekeepers have clocked the action in a 60 minute football
			game to actually be around 14 minutes. Who says americans are lazy.
		</item>
		<item>The word "funky" appears in Charles Dickens\' The Pickwick
			Papers. Here\'s the context "And so he did the funky chicken."
		</item>
		<item>A domestic cat has eighteen claws: five on each of its front
			paws and four on each of its back paws... Unless your a stupid black
			cat and have 5 raptor claws on the back of each foot.</item>
		<item>The tip of a whip makes a cracking sound because it is moving
			faster than the speed of sound- much like a fart.</item>
		<item>An ear of corn almost always has an even number of rows
			(twelve, fourteen, or sixteen).</item>
		<item>Earthworms have five hearts. Shame they don\'t have any courage
			or brains.</item>
		<item>Whale vomit is used in perfume and the flavoring of dried
			fruit and tobacco. That\'s why norwegian pineapples smell funny.
		</item>
		<item>All Polar bears are left handed. They will also eat you if you
			ask them about it.</item>
		<item>Americans on average eat 18 acres of pizza every day.
			Unfortunately none of it is used for commercial development of
			housing.</item>
		<item>China has more English speakers than the United States. They
			love you long time.</item>
		<item>If you fart consistently for 6 years and 9 months, enough gas
			is produced to create the energy of an atomic bomb. SWEET I\'M A WMD!
		</item>
		<item>If you keep a goldfish in a dark room, it will eventually turn
			white.</item>
		<item>Leonardo Da Vinci invented the scissors. oh, and other stuff
			too.</item>
		<item>If the population of China walked past you in single file, the
			line would never end because of the rate of reproduction.</item>
		<item>The ant always falls over on its right side when intoxicated.
			I\'ve seen some drunk-ass ants before, and it\'s true.</item>
		<item>It is NOT impossible to lick your elbow.</item>
		<item>A shrimp\'s heart is in its head. that\'s why I kill them when I
			punch them in the face.</item>
		<item>It is physically impossible for pigs to look up into the sky,
			unless you get some rope an anvil and a pulley.</item>
		<item>A pregnant goldfish is called a twit. You don\'t want to know
			what two of them are called.</item>
		<item>Between 1937 and 1945 Heinz produced a version of Alphabetic
			Spaghetti specially for the German market that consisted solely of
			little pasta swastikas. Wait, this one isn\'t true.</item>
		<item>More than 50% of the people in the world have never made or
			received a telephone call. It\'s cause they\'re poor.</item>
		<item>Rats and horses can\'t vomit. They just projectile poo.</item>
		<item>The "sixth sick sheik\'s sixth sheep\'s sick" is said to be the
			toughest tongue twister in the English language. My record is saying
			it 6 times without messing up.</item>
		<item>If you sneeze too hard, you can fracture a rib. If you try to
			suppress a sneeze, you can rupture a blood vessel in your head or
			neck and die.</item>
		<item>Rats multiply so quickly that in 18 months, two rats could
			have over a million descendants. They\'re horny little buggers. I
			should invent Rat Condoms. But then I\'d have to put them on them and
			that\'s gross.</item>
		<item>Wearing headphones for just an hour will increase the bacteria
			in your ear by 700 times.</item>
		<item>Thirty-five percent of the people who use personal ads for
			dating are already married.</item>
		<item>23% of all photocopier faults worldwide are caused by people
			sitting on them and photocopying their asses. I\'ve destroyed 37
			myself.</item>
		<item>In the course of an average lifetime you will, while sleeping,
			eat 70 assorted insects and 10 spiders. This does not include
			scorpions.</item>
		<item>On average, 100 people choke to death on ballpoint pens every
			year. Darwin is proud.</item>
		<item>A snail can sleep for three years. It\'s bad when you make
			Laharl look good.</item>
		<item>Our eyes are always the same size from birth, but our nose and
			ears never stop growing. That\'s why babies have misshappen alien
			heads and old guys have floppy ears.</item>
		<item>The electric chair was invented by a dentist. Figures.
		</item>
		<item>"Typewriter" is the longest word that can be made using the
			letters only on one row of the keyboard.</item>
		<item>"Go." is the shortest complete sentence in the English
			language. Next up is "Die." I\'ve see a couple of mages use that but
			they didn\'t point at me.</item>
		<item>If Barbie were life-size, her measurements would be 39-23-33.
			She would stand seven feet, two inches tall. What a freak.</item>
		<item>The average fart travels over 16 feet when released. That\'s
			really nasty.</item>
		<item>An ant can live underwater for over 14 days.</item>
		<item>Camels have a straight spine despite their hump. Heh, I said
			hump.</item>
		<item>In some places in Egypt it is free to use the restroom but you
			must bring/buy your own toilet paper. </item>
		<item>The pickle while only containing 7 calories has no nutritional
			value. Dill pickles have more calories than sweet ones, which only
			have 6.</item>
		<item>I just wet myself.</item>
		<item>You smell like poop. HAHA</item>
		<item>Drutro is also known as ULTRAWANG</item>
		<item>Oranges, lemons, watermelons, pineapples and tomatoes are
			berries.</item>
		<item>Mexico once invaded Spain because they felt they were over
			taxed.</item>
		<item>Colas were not originally carbonated.</item>
		<item>It takes a whole coffee tree to result in one pound of roasted
			beans.</item>
		<item>It\'s estimated that only 1 in 10 people actually use their
			pens till they run out of ink.</item>
		<item>Women\'s hearts beat faster than men\'s.</item>
		<item>Slothiumish is the name given to chronic laziness, it causes
			12 deaths worldwide per year. </item>
		<item>Emus cannot walk backwards. </item>
		<item>The turbines of an aircraft can oporate for over 10,000 hours
			without getting fatigued.</item>
		<item>The toque was invented in Canada. I have no idea what that is.</item>
		<item>Rubber comes from trees. Blubber grows on knees.</item>
		<item>Eating instant noodles more than twice weekly is has been
			shown to lower your IQ.</item>
		<item>The earth is .02 degrees warmer when there is a full moon.
		</item>
		<item>Many hospitals sell umbilical cords which are used in vein
			transplant sugary.</item>
		<item>AM (radio) stands for \'ample magnetics\'.</item>
		<item>Of all professions, bus driving makes the most people go
			insane.</item>
		<item>The last name Hayward was originally given to fence
			inspectors.</item>
		<item>A female lobster is referred to as a hen. </item>
		<item>There is technically no such thing as a male cow. Take that Back at the Barnyard.</item>
		<item>Piranhas paticularly like bear meat.</item>
		<item>Beijing, China houses the worlds biggest McDonalds.</item>
		<item>Austrailia has over 70,000 followers of "Jedi".</item>
		<item>Seven percent of the population is left handed.</item>
		<item>Koalas aren\'t related to bears let alone actually being them.
		</item>
		<item>The origional typewriter had 27 letters.</item>
		<item>Chairs have only been around since 250bc.</item>
		<item>Reindeer are quite simply male deer.</item>
		<item>Plastic is made from oil. Drive less to save a lawnchair.</item>
		<item>Lutherans believe that Lex Luthor is their saviour.</item>
		<item>Chewing gum is illegal in Singapore.</item>
		<item>There are three kinds of snakes that can glide.</item>
		<item>Glass is a slow moving liquid.</item>
		<item>One trree can filter out 60 pounds of polutants per year.
		</item>
		<item>Olympic is the greek word for gigantic.</item>
		<item>If you fire a gun into a steel wall the bullet will go back
			down the barrel and explode.</item>
		<item>A mole can dig a tunnel up to 300 feet long in just one night.
		</item>
		<item>The mutilation of monkeys was only banned through a United
			Nations resolution in 1991.</item>
		<item>String ranks number 9 on the top list of choking hazards.
		</item>
		<item>You can go without sleep longer than you can without water.
		</item>
		<item>Only 1/10 people don\'t dream.</item>
		<item>Bouncy balls are banned in most US highschools.</item>
		<item>Some dogs can\'t bark.</item>
		<item>Tokyo only has 100 trees in it.</item>
		<item>A duckling once told me celery is great after a good pee.
		</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>