<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="wwzdstrings">
        <item>I\'d buy a yak, paint it blue, and consider the problem solved</item>
        <item>I\'d build an Ark, and I\'d build a big room for poo. I\'d call it the poop deck... HAH!</item>
        <item>I\'d run away screaming.</item>
        <item>Figure out where the problem lies, and then punch it in the face for lying.</item>
        <item>I\'d hit it.</item>
        <item>I\'d provide a distraction by faking a convulsion.</item>
        <item>I\'d eat a handful of dirt.</item>
        <item>I\'d pee in your shoes... again.</item>
        <item>I\'d draw a stick figure stabbing a cow.</item>
        <item>I\'d wet the bed.</item>
        <item>I\'d hogtie someone and spit grape gogurt on them.</item>
        <item>I\'d introduce club to face.</item>
        <item>I honestly have no idea what I\'d do.</item>
        <item>I\'d try solving for X first.</item>
        <item>I\'d check and see if history was repeating itself.</item>
        <item>I\'d go rock climbing.</item>
        <item>I\'d wait till you were asleep, squirt lotion all over your face, and take a picture of a stuffed animal humping your face.</item>
        <item>I\'d have sex with a donkey.</item>
        <item>I\'d throw spoons at them for half an hour</item>
        <item>I\'d wedgie [other]</item>
        <item>I\'d push a couple old ladies down some stairs till I felt better.</item>
        <item>I\'d find the source of the problem and debug it.</item>
        <item>I\'d kick drutro in the jimmy</item>
        <item>I\'d beat an old man senseless with a 2x4</item>
        <item>I\'d set wonko\'s hair on fire.</item>
        <item>I\'d club ogg then grunt a lot.</item>
        <item>I\'d set some rope, a midget and beat the candy out of it pinata style.</item>
        <item>I\'d scream.</item>
        <item>I\'d give myself a tattoo with Lye.</item>
        <item>I\'d eat an entire tub of lard.</item>
        <item>I\'d put a dead cat in a box and give it to you as a birthday present, then tell you "I was gonna give it to you last year but forgot it in the closet."</item>
        <item>I\'d throw eggs at it.</item>
        <item>I\'d pick up a club and hit it.</item>
        <item>I\'d teach a man how to fish so he\'d give fish instead of me giving him fish because that\'s just dumb.</item>
        <item>Two words:  Angry Dragon...</item>
        <item>I\'d stop talking and start kicking ass!</item>
        <item>I\'d break things.</item>
        <item>I\'d throw a chair like Steve Balmer.</item>
        <item>I\'d invade a small country.</item>
        <item>I\'d burn every book I could find about animal husbandry because THEY DON\'T HELP.</item>
        <item>I\'d blame the French. Or Goblins. Close enough.</item>
        <item>I\'d invite the neighbors over then burn their house down. Unless it was connected to my house.</item>
        <item>I\'d hide under the desk until the bad people go away.</item>
        <item>I\'d get on the phone then yell "SCREW YOU" and slam the phone down.</item>
        <item>I\'d go get some steak!</item>
        <item>I\'d go beat the candy out of some little people.</item>
        <item>I\'d hide under a bed until someone laid down then make scary sounds.</item>
        <item>I\'d...  I\'d... crap, I\'d do something amusing I guess.</item>
        <item>I\'d start by taking off my pants.</item>
        <item>I\'d inform you I\'m not wearing any knickers.</item>
        <item>I\'d randomly select someone from the channel and set their hair on fire.</item>
        <item>I\'d do the funky chicken.</item>
        <item>I\'d write a story of my adventures travelling with an angry penguin named Rufus.</item>
        <item>I\'d start chanting "Developers! Developers! Developers!" then throw a chair.</item>
        <item>I\'d collect some teeth and make a necklace.</item>
        <item>I\'d think outside the box after developing a synergy with my core competencies</item>
        <item>I\'d go back in time and threaten Steve jobs with a good clubbing aboust the head if he decided to go with a one button mouse.</item>
        <item>I\'d travel into the future and challenge myself to a fight, knowing I\'d lose.</item>
        <item>WTF do you always ask me? asshat.</item>
        <item>It would be better perhaps if I didn\'t tell. The police are monitoring this channel after my last response.</item>
        <item>I think you\'re a fed so I\'m not gonna answer</item>
        <item>I\'d scream "HAVE AT THEE!" and pelt them with rasins</item>
        <item>I\'d throw beanbags at them and scream "Lightningbolt! Lightningbolt! Lightningbolt!" and give up any chance of ever having sex with a real woman ever again.</item>
        <item>I\'d read a book.</item>
        <item>I\'d talk like a pirate for the rest of the day.</item>
        <item>I\'d strap a goblin to my back and walk through an open market.</item>
        <item>I\'d piss in your cornflakes while you weren\'t looking.</item>
        <item>I\'d put a salamander in your shirt.</item>
        <item>I\'d build a 1/16 scale model of an orc out of earwax.</item>
        <item>I\'d probably babble incoherently for a couple hours, then run off into the woods</item>
        <item>I\'d swing a troll around by it\'s nether-regions.</item>
        <item>I\'d poke a muskrat with a pencil and call him Lucy.</item>
        <item>I\'d hire a polka band and celebrate the chinese newyear early.</item>
        <item>I\'d kick guido in the teeth and tell him he\'s a horrible actor.</item>
        <item>I\'d DOMINATE doomboardgame.</item>
        <item>I\'d play a game of checkers against a dog.</item>
        <item>I\'d make a bootleg CD of "sounds from the mens bathroom."</item>
        <item>I\'d cover myself with honey and roll around in a beehive.</item>
        <item>I\'d fill the bed with mac and cheese.</item>
        <item>I\'d commit genocide. But only against people with hair.</item>
        <item>I\'d hit you with a limp wombat.</item>
        <item>I\'d make animal sounds.</item>
        <item>I\'d use a rabbit as a pillow because they\'re fluffy.</item>
        <item>I\'d punch you right in the stupid face. That\'s the one on your head.</item>
        <item>I\'d lick a penny.</item>
        <item>I\'d put on a wool shirt and run through a carwash.</item>
        <item>I\'d kick a puppy.</item>
        <item>I\'d slap [other].</item>
        <item>I\'d eat 42 deviled eggs.</item>
        <item>I\'d do a little jig.</item>
        <item>I\'d fight a Weebol to the death- I hear they wobble but they don\'t fall down.</item>
        <item>I\'d lick a rubber aardvark. They taste like ants but don\'t bite as much as the real thing.</item>
        <item>I\'d whet the bed.</item>
        <item>I\'d eat some rubber buggy baby burger bites three times fast.</item>
        <item>I\'d fire a bucket of monkeys out of a giant cannon.</item>
        <item>I\'d cover you in holandaise sauce and then offer you a towel.</item>
        <item>I\'d have some private time with your keyboard... wait, that was last week...</item>
    </string-array>
    
</resources>
